for sharing your story so that's what's
different about me and I learned that
because uh I had I myot most recent
tedex speaking coach he said that every
talk should be a gift to your
audience every talk should be a gift to
your audience audience yes and and you
know can you elaborate can you explain
what that means yeah absolutely because
when most people speak the uh we we have
a natural tendency to talk about
ourselves and that's normal but H how
can we frame out the content so that
it's so it's so it's more focused on the
benefit for your
audience exactly now um how do you the
one question um for you is how do you
create and deliver engaging webinar
presentations that sell because a lot of
us uh
a lot of us um have a hard time you know
like we get on camera but it's really
hard to monetize so how do you create
presentations that actually
sell there's a lot of uh uh uh elements
that
[Music]
how's it going folks this is Ryan Perez
with go live and prosper um how are you
guys doing today I am in the studio with
um I uh hold on one second I think he
just uh stepped out for five seconds
uh hold on
yeah he's and he's back so yes so uh
welcome to go live and prosper my name
is Ryan Perez and I am you know proudly
representing uh boat tie creative we are
a um a Consulting agency uh digital or
sorry creative agency uh we we do uh
websites Graphics marketing Etc and um I
would like to to um first um just uh
thank everybody that has supported um
you know the hustle Zone Network um so
far we have uh you know a subscriber
base of over
30,000 people and that has happened in
the last year so thank you guys to all
of our loyal um you know supporters and
subscribers and um the other thing too
is that we uh we are getting ourselves
set up for all of the podcast networks
and we actually got approved for go live
and prosper so um uh so now you can find
this particular episode on uh iTunes and
Spotify and some of the other uh and
Google uh podcasts and some of the other
podcast networks and uh so I'm I'm super
excited about that so um if anyone's in
the comments um feel free to comment
we're we'll try our best to um answer
some of your questions um we only got 30
minutes so I'm going to try to uh do the
best that I can to um um you know to to
answer your questions but please please
comment let me know in the comment
description um if you're here and um you
know please stay for the full interview
because I promise you my guests will be
very entertaining uh after his American
Idol audition William hung's rendition
of She Bangs became famous for all the
wrong reasons despite a humbling start
will redeemed himself he has since
appeared on Jimmy Kimmel Live Ellen
degenerous show and even performed with
Ricky Martin in Las Vegas William has
spent the last few years studying the
world's top performers um and um public
speakers to uncover the secrets to
success um using his discovered uh sorry
using what he discovered he skyrocketed
his first studio album inspiration uh to
number one on the independent Billboard
Chart uh his latest tedex talk has been
viewed by over 35,000 people in less
than a month and he's also spoken for
Microsoft Remax uh uh corvo and other
esteemed associations he now helps
purpos driven uh business owners become
champions in their industries by
leveraging Public public speaking
um he helps them uncover their unique in
inspiring stories and uses them to book
and sell out their stages uh webinars
and live streams so that's amazing I
want you guys to welcome or before I
welcome our guest I'm G to play his um
um I'm gonna play his uh video reel so
give me a few
seconds and um I I currently studying at
UC Berkeley right now uh but it's kind
of odd like why I chose to even audition
in the first place
because She Bangs She Bang I'm by the
thank you you can't sing you can't dance
so what do you what do you want me to
say thank you you can't sing you can't
dance so what you want me to say at that
moment I had a choice get get upset like
the other
contestants or stay positive and set a
new
[Music]
example you're no longer singing you're
going in a completely different
direction you're actually in town
because you're going to be speaking at a
Ted X Chula Vista tomorrow what is this
New Path you're on I'm trying to inspire
other people I'm a inspirational speaker
I want people to choose happiness in
their lives now raise your hand if you
want to experience this kind of
lifechanging
opportunity I really loved your
presentation it was very uplifting and
very sincere and very real and very
encouraging and inspiring thank you very
much absolutely courageous authentic I
love that you owned it William I love
how you came to our Global sales conf
and Incorporated our Champions theme and
everything you talked about you related
your experiences to our group and you
were just phenomenal you have great
courage great confidence and you just
inspired us all thank you got my team
excited and Powerful that they can win
and we so relatable it was so
approachable you use simple words but it
was so effective and very inspired I
feel that regardless if I'm doing
performing or speaking or other
appearances my main goal is to have
people smile choose to create it choose
to be
happy he was incredibly inspirational uh
I have some fears going forwards into
the to the workplace um but he managed
to convince me that they're all in my
head and that I has nothing at all to
worry about so hearing his
entrepreneurial Spirit hearing how he
took that one giant leap to make a
difference for others was very impactful
all the heat that was coming on you from
the whole country and the whole world
and how you just took it with Grace and
you laughed and you enjoyed yourself and
stay stuck with who you were that that
was such a hero story to give that gift
to others to encourage them to expand
Beyond where they are into whatever it
is that they would choose to Williams
presentation was really entertaining and
very informative how do you find
happiness and how do you discover
yourself whenever I hear
it's it's very touching thank you
William for being there us what you
shared with us in your conference I
think it's going to make a change for me
from now on so I wouldn't have to be
afraid anymore so thank you for sharing
your experience with us and it was so
inspiring because of the way he
encouraged us to continue moving forward
no matter what the obstacle may be
appreciate his inspiration and inspires
me to move forward in my own business
thank you William
awesome that was a great demo reel and
um so uh I won't let you guys wait any
further everyone please welcome William
Hung hey how's it going my friend he I'm
doing I'm doing
great yeah sorry you weren't able to see
the video hey no that's why I was like
wait what's going on
yeah yeah I had that's why it was uh it
was quiet there but sorry about that but
either way well welcome to um uh go live
and prosper um it's it's great to have
you as a guest and you know um how how
has it been like what have you been up
to uh I'm excited that I'm building a
new online coaching program to help more
people find their stories within them so
that they can capture attention and
increase influence
awesome awesome so uh let's take it back
a bit you know when I was uh you know in
my 20s I was watching a show called
American Idol and um one one person that
has made and you know an impact on on my
life and a lot of of of people's life as
yourself because you went and you had
the courage to do what a lot of us
wouldn't do and you uh performed for for
um for Simon Paulo Abdul and Randy
Jackson and you became overnight an in
international Superstar so uh tell me
about that
experience well I was studying for civil
engineering at Berkeley but I was
struggling and I wasn't happy so I
figured that I need something different
to do in my life and then one day I saw
this poster for school time show at the
clock Cur dories I figured why not
there's nothing to lose so I studed
watching videos from Ricky Martin and I
sang my favorite song To This Day She
Bangs by Ricky Martin and to my surprise
I won the grand prize was a DVD
player so that's what gave me the
confidence to audition for American Idol
awesome awesome and then when you uh
when you did the interview were you
embarrassed uh to see your uh to see
your uh uh footage all over all over TV
and everyone talking about
it I W I wouldn't say embarrassed
because most people they don't when they
don't make it to American Idol uh
Hollywood they show their you know their
less than optimal auditions
yeah and I and I thought you know maybe
it's not a big deal maybe nothing will
happen you know just like most people
but somehow for my audition e everything
in my life
changed wow and how did your how did
your family and friends how did they all
um uh receive it when it all
happened my parents were shocked it's
like what how could you go audition for
Amer
Idol and uh and then but but when you
became famous so I mean I don't think
they were like how could you because now
you know you probably changed their
lives and you know yeah yeah when they
when they when they realized that uh
after the first year that's when they
changed their
perspective right and at the time you
were studying at Berkeley um civil
engineering is that correct yeah
yes and um but you're not doing that
anymore and how come because I wasn't
passionate about engineering
anymore you w passionate about so that's
why you kind of wanted to U because at
the time when we look at the video clip
you were talking about that you wanted
to venture into uh singing so it was
that like you thought that would be a
really good transition to you know to
leave civil engineering to pursue
something that that would give you more
joy well it's it's it's it's uh when I
it's more like when I get the record
contract deal from Kos records back then
that's when I know that I could take the
next
step yes yes yes yes yes and you so a
lot has transpired um from from since
then and you kind of migrated from uh
doing music and uh touring all over the
world you got you you had a chance to uh
sing with uh uh Ricky Martin and uh you
met a lot of celebrities but now you
wanted to venture into something else so
uh you are now a a speaker that's
teaching people how to get out of their
comfort zones um uh how to set clear
goals and and Target the right audiences
and adjusting their mindset so tell us a
little bit about your um your your new
gig well I I thought thought about uh
continuing with the entertainment
industry so what happened was that after
about four years living my dream life
everything went so went amazing I got
more than I expected uh things slowed
down and then I had to make a choice do
I want to keep going with showz or
should I get a stable job and I chose
the stable job because I thought I I
made enough money I could be you I don't
have to keep taking risk
so that's that's why at that point I
went back to finish school at Cal State
Northridge to get my degree bachelor's
degree in math uh I I I tried I tried
different jobs I try to be as math
teacher and then eventually I said I
work for the government for the last
eight years and then but then I feel
like there's more to me than hiding
behind my cubicle so that's why I
thought I I wanted to find something
else I could do outside of my
administrative uh job for sharing your
story I I so that's what's different
start public speaking and I learned that
because speaking coach
because should be a gift to started
working for the sheriff's department
every
talk find my voice again I feel like I
have you know can you elaborate can you
explain what that means somehow like re
my performance because I like
like like to be out there we have a
natural tendency have you always been
like that as a kid and that's normal but
yeah I actually
cont show my unque for your audience I
also competed in a math and science
competition was on local TV how do you
so yeah I I want to something um for you
is how do you create and deliver
engaging webinar presentations that I
mean lot of us that's
just on
camera how do you create presentations
that your brand is is pretty much your
story you know clumped up into what they
call a narrative
El you know some people's story is that
you know what I've always wanted to be
in the Limelight I've always wanted to
speak I've always wanted to you your
passions don't really change
presentation but the
in Soul in you doesn't CH what a waste
of my so you're pretty much you did it
from you know the talent show American
Idol and now you're doing it as a
speaker which is which is amazing and
playing your demo real that was amazing
to see how many people were impacted by
that's the way you're feeling that was
awesome the presentation so tell me how
do I attract high
quity for
I would say I would say high energy you
to figure what what what specific
problem straight
forward
last tip on improving coach very hard to
figure out on your own because there too
many we don't know which emplo you are
the expert emplo
Ur amazing two three or four things that
matter most the way
because she have a couple
friends like you know a good point
because you know we have so many ideas
but when it comes down to narrowing um
what our focus is it's really hard for a
lot of people especially when you're
could be your you know these podcasts
and webinars are babies so you know we
want to talk about everything we want to
do everything but you know like you said
we are the experts and you know just
tailor message especially to the Right
audience and and that was one thing that
I noticed about you is that you have the
you know how to Target the Right
audience so tell us about your targeting
um
techniques well uh like like I well this
is something I still evolving because I
only started uh building and creating
this online coaching uh business last
year uh so I I so by by working with a
few mes and a few paying clent
uh I I learned that the people that I
want to work with have a clear goal a
Clear Vision in their mind uh so it's
beyond them and it's something that's
beyond themselves uh for example one of
the most recent uh new client that I've
gotten uh she has a vision to help
change change the legislation uh for the
United States because uh her her mom
died of cancer because her aunt couldn't
get the Visa approved to come to United
States
wow yeah wow I mean she her UNT finally
made it from Vietnam uh but it's two
months too late so you know and her news
was featured on on uh on National media
so you know so she so she wants to do a
tedic talk to spread that message even
more to let people know to bring the
awareness that like what how are we
making up these rules you know how could
people that want to come to United
States save alive doesn't get priority
over people that just want to travel for
leisure so yeah so that's very powerful
so so I want to work with people like
that that have a Clear Vision uh a clear
message that's worth
spreading that's worth spreading now um
how do you get press you know because I
think that you know some of us need to
get the press and we need to you know
like in order for us to get more
speaking
engagements we need the social proof
right we need to be able to um prove to
other people that people actually want
to listen to us because without that
social proof you don't get the gig right
so how do I get the
Press well everybody has to start
somewhere um and I and I think after
experimenting uh speaking for many many
local groups uh Toast Masters is still
one of the best investments you can make
in your life uh because it's it's uh
it's because yeah like I said everybody
has to start somewhere uh Toast Masters
is like a platform for you to practice
for free uh and and not free but very
normal cost for $45 every 6 months and
then you get like instant feedback from
the audience so I would start there uh
once you do that you know get you get
comfortable with your message uh reach
out to local
organizations uh you you don't need to
wait for permission there is no right
time just do it pick up the phone ask
them uh like you know what problems and
challenges do you have for your next
event event it could be a business
networking event it could be a workshop
whatever it is ask them what they want
to accomplish from the event and then
match your expertise with
them awesome awesome awesome that's good
stuff now tell me about your
book my book is Al is uh is uh called
Champion by choice uh I started writing
it about one and a half years ago it's
finally done October last year it was a
a a
difficult Journey because I I am not
that good with written word with English
mean my second language so I needed a
lot of help uh with mentors with with uh
with uh coaches friends but I finally
got it done and the idea the main idea
of the book is how you can become a
champion in your life how you can choose
to be a champion and how people can
choose you to be a
champion so this is everyone um I'm just
going to show this quickly I'm going to
take you down here for five
seconds awesome awesome awesome okay now
we switch spots that's weird but anyway
so yeah so Champion by choice now um is
there anything else that you want to
leave with our
audience everyone no matter how boring
uh you you might think you are has an
inspiring story within you your story it
does doesn't have to be something
extraordinary it could be something that
happened everyday life through
relationships through your career
through your business through all for
your health find that sto find those
stories within you where you've
experienced faor and
frustration find a way to frame it
positively uh to benefit your audience
and share that with the
world awesome okay so we just got to our
lightning round here and I'm going to
ask you some rapid fire questions so
William U from a scale from 1 to 10 how
good are you at keeping
secrets
10 okay
um hold on one second talking or
texting
talking okay well you're from my
generation probably because uh like I
don't understand the whole texting thing
to be honest with you but anyway uh
favorite day of the
week
Sunday okay uh favorite city in the
US Los Angel the city that you live in
okay okay uh San
Francisco San Francisco okay name your
par uh name a nickname that your parents
used to call
you
ton and what is that mean uh in Chinese
uh because uh because my my Chinese name
is
uh so so can they say so means like like
like like the like the son and then and
then the the first name because they
reverse it in in the
Chinese oh that's the way way they say
your name they say it basic on your
family name first and then your first
name and then your first name okay and
that's better that's that's logically
correct right because it's better to
State the family name first then the
yeah that makes a lot of sense um last
what would you rather be able to speak
every language in the world or be able
to talk to
animals speak every language in the
world okay favorite
holiday Martin Luther King
day okay how long does it take for you
to get
ready 10
minutes okay on a scale from one to 10
how good of a driver are
you
seven okay uh fill in the bank Taylor
Swift is
amazing
artist amazing artist okay and at what
age do you want to
retire right now I'm 37 let's aim for
47 47 so in 10 years awesome and um
invis invisibility or super
strength super
strength okay and last question is it
wrong for vegetarians to eat animal
crackers
no it's not wrong really well be because
uh because I think it's a matter of
perspective I feel I feel that when you
eat uh when you eat crackers uh you
you're you're just enjoying something
that that's made up of something that's
not
animal yeah like a lion it's like don't
worry it's no one's got no one is
getting hurt by eating animal crackers
so I have to agree with you so thank you
so much uh William for coming into the
hustle Zone and um appearing on uh go
live and prosper uh there is one more uh
one more thing that I require all of my
guests to do is uh I'm gonna say welcome
to the and I need you to scream hustle
Zone as loud as you can for some high
energy so welcome to the hust hust
thank you so much William for for coming
in you have been so gracious one thing
that I really appreciate about you
William is that you when someone
messages you you message them right back
um it's it's you know you're so
humble you've accomplished so much
you've inspired so many people including
myself and you know it is uh it's it's
actually a dream come true to have you
uh on this this podcast and thank you
for being so humble so gracious and
hopefully we'll be able to uh meet again
sometime and talk about other things so
thank you so much uh William and um how
can we find you you can go to will
hung.com w l lhu ng.com uh and reach out
to me there that's my website awesome
all right well thank you so much William
and I will talk to to you later sounds
good okay awesome so there you have it
folks uh go live and prosper this is our
second episode and um yeah it was very
very awesome to have William Hung um and
a lot of us remember who he is because I
mean we all like to watch uh that that
was viral like you know the shebangs uh
moment was a viral moment but the fact
of what he's doing now and and if you
looking to get into speaking and you're
looking to do public speaking um or
you're looking to do webinars and sell
your your your your webinars uh he's
definitely the person to talk to he's a
great coach and a lot of people stand uh
by his message so thank you guys all for
tuning in to go live and prosper and I
will talk to you guys soon bye